A Guide to the Department of Confederate Military Records, 1859-1996
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Unit Records
  - Subseries 3: Infantry
    - Battalions
      - 1st (Irish)
        - Co. A (Leigh's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Co. B (Bridgford's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1862-1912 (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Co. C (Thorn's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - Co. D (Seddon's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Co. E (Jones' Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Co. F, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - Co. G, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Co. I, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904-1912 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - 4th (never organized)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - 5th
        - Co. A (Brunswick Guard), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Co. C (Prince George Rifle Rangers), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - Co. D (Varina Artillery), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - Co. E (Dinwiddie Guards), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - Capt. Chappel's Co., n.d. (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - Capt. Capt. Jarvis' Co., n.d. (Box 30, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - 7th (merged with 61st Regt.)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - 9th (merged with 25th Regt.)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - 22nd
        - Co. A (Burfoot's Co), 1864 (Box 30, Folder 20)
        - Co. B (Charlotte & Lunenburg Arty), 1864-1938 (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - Co. D (Jackson's Co.), 1864 (Box 30, Folder 22)
        - Co. E (Elam's Co.), 1864 (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - Co. G (Johnson's Co.), 1864-1912 (Box 30, Folder 24)
        - Co. H (Bowles' Co.), 1864-1911 (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - Co. I (Farrar's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Co. K (Hanes' Co.), 1914 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - 23rd
        - Co. A (Blessing's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 28)
        - Co. B (Dunlap's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 29)
        - Co. C (Gose's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 30)
        - Co. D (Cecil's Co.), 1913 (Box 30, Folder 31)
        - Co. E (Buchanan's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 32)
        - Co. F (McDonald's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 33)
        - Co. G (Beckley's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 34)
        - Co. H (Barnes' Co.), 1913 (Box 30, Folder 35)
        - Co. I (Arnick's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 36)
        - Co. K, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - 26th
        - Co. A (Charleston Sharpshooters), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 39)
        - Co. B (Read's Co.), 1906 (Box 30, Folder 40)
        - Co. C (Thompson's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 41)
        - Co. D (Edgar's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 42)
        - Co. E (Hefner's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 43)
        - Co. F (Red Sulpher Yankee Hunters), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 44)
        - Co. G (White Sulpher Rifles), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 45)
        - Co. H (Dunlap's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 46)
        - Co. I (Carr's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 47)
        - Co. K, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 48)
        - Miscellaneous, 1886-1907 (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - 30th
        - Co. A (Adams' Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 50)
        - Co. B (French's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 51)
        - Co. C (Western Artillery), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 52)
        - Co. D (Vawter's Co.), 1907 (Box 30, Folder 53)
        - Co. E (Hoffman's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 54)
        - Co. F (Armstrong's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 55)
        - Co. I, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 56)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - 44th
        - Co. A (Hinton's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 58)
        - Co. B (Branch's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 59)
        - Co. C (Morrison's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 60)
        - Co. D (Hinton's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 61)
        - Co. E (Thomas' Co.), 1923 (Box 30, Folder 62)
        - Co. I, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 63)
        - Miscellaneous, 1913 (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - 45th
        - Co. A (Stallings' Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 65)
        - Co. B (Buchanan's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 66)
        - Co. C (Cook's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 67)
        - Co. D (Justice's Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 68)
        - Co. E (Ellis' Co.), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 69)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 70)
      - Independent Companies
        - Avis' Co. (Provost Guard), n.d. (Box 30, Folder 71)
        - Hutter's Co. (Southern Guard) & Tosh's Co. (Sons of Liberty) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1861-1911 (Box 30, Folder 72)
        - Taylor's Co. (Young Guard), 1916 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Subseries 4: Local Defense Troops
    - 1st Battalion Va. Cavalry
      - Co. A (Wood's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Co. B (Haywood's Co.), 1912 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Co. C (Norfleet's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 1st (Armory) Battalion Va. Infantry
      - Co. A (Ayres' Co.), 1906-1914 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Co. B (Forsyth's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Co. C (Suddith's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Co. D (Fitzgerald's Co.), 1911-1914 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Co. F (Barker's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 2nd (Quartermaster) Battalion Va. Infantry (Co.'s A-F), 1902-1919 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 3rd Regiment Va. Artillery, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 3rd (Departmental) Battalion Va. Infantry
      - Co. A (War Department Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Co. B (Reagan Rifles), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Co. C (Jamison's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Co. D (Treasury Guards, 2nd Co.), 1911 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Co. E (Q.M. Dept. Volunteers), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Co. F (Baker's Co.), 1905 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Co. G (2nd) (Gay's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), ca. 1864-1914 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Co. H (Memminger Guards), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Co. I (Pace's Co.), 1905 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Co. K (Dill's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - 4th (Naval) Battalion Infantry
      - Co. A (Curlin's Co.), 1912-1914 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Co. B (Constantine's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Co. C (Pettit's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Co. D (Boushell's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Co. E (Brown's Co.), 1914 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - 5th (Arsenal) Battalion Infantry
      - Co. A (1st) (Zimmer's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 27)
      - Co. B (Brown's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - Co. E (Browne's Co.), 1915 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - Co. F (Ennis' Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Co. G (Sloat's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Co. H (Haywood's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - 6th (Tredegar) Battalion Infantry
      - Co. A (Derbyshire's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Co. B (McDonald's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Co. C (Neal's Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - 7th (Nitre & Mining Bureau) Battalion Infantry, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - 25th (Richmond City) Battalion Infantry
      - Co. A (Greener's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1914 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Co. B (Bossieux's (Louis) Co.), 1884 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Co. C, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 39)
      - Co. D (Richmond Minute Men), 1911 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - Co. E (Maule's Co.), 1909 (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - Co. F (Bossieux's (Cyrus) Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 7) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1862-ca. 1887 (Box 31, Folder 42)
      - Co. G (President's Guard), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 43)
      - Co. H (Allison's Co.), 1915 (Box 31, Folder 44)
      - Miscellaneous, 1894 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Chappell's Co. (Pickett Guard) (Petersburg), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - King's Co. (Saltville Artillery) (Smyth Co.), 1916 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Shank's Co. (Fauquier Co.), n.d. (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Subseries 5: Reserves
    - Regiments
      - 1st
        - Co. B (Prince Edward Reserves), 1921 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Co. C (Chamber's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Co. D (Hurt's Co.), 1911 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Co. E (Branch's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), ca. 1898-1915 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Co. F (Nottoway Reserves) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1864 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Co. G (Chesterfield Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Co. I (Powhatan Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Co. K (Lunenburg Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 2nd
        - Co. B, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Co. C, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Co. D, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Co. E, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Co. F, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - 3rd
        - Field & Staff, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Co. A (Amherst Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Co. B (Campbell Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Co. C (Buckingham Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - Co. F (Campbell Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Co. G (Lynchburg Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Co. H (Nelson Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - Co. I (Appomattox Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Co. K (Botetourt Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - 4th
        - Co. A (Botetourt Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - Co. B (Grayson Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - Co. C (Pulaski Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - Co. D (Montgomery Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - Co. F (Carroll Reserves), 1914 (Box 32, Folder 27)
        - Co. G (Wythe Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 28)
        - Co. H (Floyd Reserves) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1900 (Box 32, Folder 29)
        - Co. I (Floyd Reserves) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1900 (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - Co. K (Carroll Reserves), 1914 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Battalions
      - 1st
        - Co. D (Perkins' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 32)
        - Co. E (Malone's Co.), 1910 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - Co. G (Stiff's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 34)
        - Co. H (Madison Reserves), 1920 (Box 32, Folder 35)
        - Co. I (Kasey's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 36)
        - Co. K, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 37)
        - Miscellaneous, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - 2nd
        - Co. C (Norment's Co.), 1919 (Box 32, Folder 39)
        - Co. D (Cook's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 40)
        - Co. E (Botetourt Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 41)
        - Co. F (Miller's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 42)
        - Co. G (Hunter's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 43)
        - Co. H (Bradley's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 44)
        - Co. I (Ellis' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 45)
      - 3rd
        - Co. A (Petersburg Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 46)
        - Co. B (Dinwiddie Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 47)
        - Co. C (Prince George Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 48)
        - Co. D (Petersburg Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 49)
        - Co. E (Petersburg Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 50)
        - Co. G, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 51)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 52)
      - 4th
        - Co. B (Shands' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 53)
        - Co. C (Griffin's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 54)
        - Co. D (Britt's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 55)
        - Co. E, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 56)
      - 5th
        - Co. A (Hairston's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 57)
        - Co. B (Powell's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 58)
        - Co. C (Moorman's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 59)
        - Co. D (Meadow's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 60)
        - Co. E (Sykes' Co.), 1861 (Box 32, Folder 61)
        - Co. F (Perkins' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 62)
        - Co. G (Arrington's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 63)
        - Co. H (Rice's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 64)
        - Co. I (Reynold's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 65)
        - Co. K, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 66)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 67)
      - 6th
        - Co. B (Graham's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 68)
        - Co. C (Campbell's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 69)
        - Co. D (Richardson's Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 70)
        - Co. E (Roberts' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 71)
        - Co. F (Barrow's Co.), 1912 (Box 32, Folder 72)
        - Co. H (Sterns' Co.), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 73)
      - 7th
        - Co. B (Rockingham Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 74)
        - Co. D (Augusta Reserves), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 75)
      - 9th, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 76)
      - 10th, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 77)
      - 11th, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - County Reserves (Unspecified Unit)
      - Albemarle County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 79)
      - Caroline County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 80)
      - Charlotte County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 81)
      - Essex County, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 82)
      - Franklin County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 83)
      - Halifax County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 84)
      - Mecklenburg County, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 85)
      - Petersburg City, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - Subseries 6: Home Guard
    - Albemarle County, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Augusta County (Staunton Home Guard), n.d. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bedford County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Bland County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Brunswick County, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Buchanan County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Chesterfield County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Henrico County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Henry County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - King & Queen County, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - King William County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lynchburg City, 1894 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Patrick County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Pittsylvania County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Powhatan County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Rappahannock County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Richmond City, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Richmond County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Roanoke County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Russell County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Smyth County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Washington County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Westmoreland County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Wythe County, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 7: Virginia State Line
    - Officers, 1906 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Regiments
      - 1st
        - Co. A (Taylor's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 12), 1863 (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Co. B (Elkin's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 12), 1863 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Co. E (Dempsey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1863-1864 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Co. K (Chambers' Co.), 1863-1864 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 2nd
        - Field & Staff, 1914 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 4th
        - Co. C (Chase's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 12), 1862-1864 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - 5th
        - Co. I (McComas's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 12), 1862 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Battalions
      - Jackson's Bn. Va. Arty.
        - Co. B (Oliver's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 12), 1863 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 8: Militia
    - Regiments
      - 1st (146th) (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 2nd (97th) (3rd Division, 7th Brigade) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 3rd (136th) (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - 4th (58th) (3rd Division, 7th Brigade) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - 5th (2nd Division, 1st Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - 15th (4th Division, 8th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - 17th (1st Division, 4th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - 19th (4th Division, 2nd Brigade) (2nd Regt. State Reserves)
        - Co. A (Atkinson's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1864 (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - Co. B (Epps' Co.) (Governor's Mounted Guard), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - Co. C (Bidgood's Co.), 1864 (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Co. D (Ward's Co.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - Co. F (Charter's Co.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - Co. G (Ruth's Co.), 1864 (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - Co. H (German Home Guards) (See Also Oversized - Box 7), 1884 (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - Co. I (Virginia Central R.R. Guard), 1861-1864 (Box 35, Folder 15)
        - Co. K (French City Guards), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 16)
        - Co. M (Kindervater's Co.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 17)
        - Co. N (Stewart's Co.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous, 1913 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - 20th, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - 21st (4th Division, 14th Brigade)
        - Co. D (Teagle's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - 25th (2nd Division, 5th Brigade) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - 29th (4th Division, 8th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - 31st (3rd Division, 16th Brigade)
        - Co. F (Yeakley's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 24)
        - Co. I (Eddy's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - 33rd (4th Division, 2nd Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - 38th (2nd Division, 3rd Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - 39th (1st Division, 15th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - 40th (2nd Division, 3rd Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - 41st (4th Division, 14th Brigade)
        - Co. B (Rockwell's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - 43rd (1st Division, 12th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - 44th (2nd Division, 5th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - 45th (2nd Division, 5th Brigade)
        - Co. G (Randall's Co.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - 46th (3rd Division, 18th Brigade) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 13), 1864 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - 47th (2nd Division, 3rd Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - 49th (1st Division, 4th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - 51st (3rd Division, 16th Brigade)
        - Field & Staff, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 37)
        - Co. A (Brinker's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 38)
        - Co. B (Marks' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 39)
        - Co. C (Willis' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 40)
        - Co. D (Prefid's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 41)
        - Co. E (Larrick's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 42)
        - Co. F (Pierce's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 43)
        - Co. G (Pifer's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      - 52nd (4th Division, 2nd Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 45)
      - 54th (4th Division, 9th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - 55th (3rd Division, 16th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - 58th (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - 59th (4th Division, 8th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - 61st (4th Division, 14th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 50)
      - 63rd (1st Division, 11th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 51)
      - 64th (1st Division, 12th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 52)
      - 67th (3rd Division, 16th Brigade), 1861-1862 (Box 35, Folder 53)
      - 69th, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 54)
      - 74th (4th Division, 2nd Brigade)
        - Co. C (Hendrick's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 13), 1860-1861 (Box 35, Folder 55)
        - Co. E (Hooper's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 13), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - 75th (5th Division, 26th Brigade), 1862 (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - 77th (3rd Division, 18th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Hartman's Co.) (See Oversized - Box 7), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 58)
        - Co. C (Inskeep's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 59)
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 60)
      - 79th (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - 1st Co. (Taylor's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 61)
        - 2nd Co. (Surbaugh's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 62)
        - 3rd Co. (Samples' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 63)
        - 4th Co. (McClung's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 64)
        - 5th Co. (Keeny's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 65)
      - 82nd (2nd Division, 1st Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 66)
      - 85th (2nd Division, 5th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 67)
      - 86th (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Gerald's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 68)
        - Co. B (Weisiger's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 69)
        - Co. C (Bane's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 70)
        - Co. D (Porterfield's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 71)
        - Co. E (Hare's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 72)
        - Co. F (Johnston's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 73)
        - 87th (Includes 9th) (4th Division, 14th Brig.), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 74)
        - 89th (3rd Division, 16th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 75)
        - 91st (1st Division, 12th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 76)
      - 92nd (4th Division, 14th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Currell's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1862 (Box 35, Folder 77)
        - Co. B (Williams' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 78)
        - Co. C (Norris' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 14), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 79)
      - 95th (4th Division, 9th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 80)
      - 97th (3rd Division, 7th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 81)
      - 104th (3rd Division, 10th Brigade), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 82)
      - 108th (5th Division, 19th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Ballentine's Co) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 83)
        - Co. B (Ruddell's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 84)
        - Co. C (Lemon's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1862 (Box 35, Folder 85)
        - Co. D (Budd's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 86)
        - Co. E (Figgart's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 87)
        - Co. F (Sam's Co.), (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 88)
        - Co. G (McNeer's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 89)
      - 109th (4th Division, 14th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Boss' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 90)
        - Co. B (Barrick's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 35, Folder 91)
      - 110th (1st Division, 12th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - 111th (4th Division, 14th Brigade)
        - 2nd Co. (Sanford's (R.J.) Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - 4th Co. (Healey's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - 5th Co. (Sanford's (Lucius) Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - 8th Co. (Deatley's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - 114th (3rd Division, 18th Brigade), n.d. (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - 115th (4th Division, 9th Brigade) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - 122nd (3rd Division, 16th Brigade)
        - Co. A (Nunn's Co.) (See Also Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861-1922 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Co. D (1st) (Anderson's Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 15), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - 128th (5th Division, 13th Brigade)
        - Co. E, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - 129th (5th Division, 27th Brigade)
        - 1st Co. (Chambers' Co.) (See Oversized - Drawer 16), 1861 (Box 36, Folder 12)